[
    {"id": "0.05558064207434654", "title": "Sports", "questions": [
        {"title": "Do you watch footbal?", "id": "0.5957863074727356", "type": "single", "answers": ["What is that?", "Yes.", "No", "Why are you asking?"], "question": "Do you watch footbal?"},
        {"title": "How many football clubs are there in England?", "id": "0.6928226856980473", "type": "single", "answers": ["11", "between 1 and 100", "25"], "question": "How many football clubs are there in England?"},
        {"title": "Which is your favourite sport?", "id": "0.8843110320158303", "type": "single", "answers": ["Football", "Voleyball", "Snooker", "Swimming"], "question": "Which is your favourite sport?"}
    ], "summary": "General sports questions"},
    {"id": "0.09178854082711041", "title": "Maths", "questions": [
        {"title": "How much is 2 + 2", "id": "0.18988746241666377", "type": "single", "answers": ["4", "2", "1", "3 tomatos"], "question": "How much is 2 + 2"},
        {"title": "Can you divide 10 by 2", "id": "0.7096117534674704", "type": "single", "answers": ["Nooooo", "YEZZZZ", "May be", "Who cares?"], "question": "Can you divide 10 by 2"},
        {"title": "1 + 1 + 1 + 1 = ?", "id": "0.7561958932783455", "type": "single", "answers": ["1", "0", "5"], "question": "1 + 1 + 1 + 1 = ?"}
    ], "summary": "Some maths questions"},
    {"id": "1", "title": "Food", "summary": "A collection of food-related questions", "questions": [
        {"id": "1", "question": "What did you have for supper last night?", "title": "What did you have for supper last night?", "type": "single", "answers": ["Youghurt", "Vanilla icecream", "Steak", "Fish and chips", "Tomatos"]},
        {"id": "2", "question": "What are your favourite vegetables ?", "title": "What are your favourite vegetables ?", "type": "multiple", "answers": ["Cucumber", "Tomatos", "Spinach", "Eggplants", "Peppers"]},
        {"id": "3", "question": "How often do you have meat?", "title": "How often do you have meat?", "type": "single", "answers": ["Every day", "Three times a week", "Every now and then", "All the time", "Never"]},
        {"id": "4", "question": "Do you like peanut butter?", "title": "Do you like peanut butter?", "type": "single", "answers": ["Yes, a ton", "Sort of", "At times", "No", "Next question please"]},
        {"title": "How much salt do you consume?", "id": "5", "type": "single", "answers": ["A lot", "Not too much", "Enough"], "question": "How much salt do you consume?"}
    ]},
    {"id": "2", "title": "Animals", "summary": "All sorts of questions about animals", "questions": [
        {"id": "22", "question": "What is your favourite animal?", "title": "What is your favourite animal?", "type": "multiple", "answers": ["Cat", "Dog", "Squirrel", "Bear", "Lion"]},
        {"title": "Have you ever ridden a horse?", "id": "0.5274261061567813", "type": "single", "answers": ["Yes", "No"], "question": "Have you ever ridden a horse?"},
        {"title": "What is your favourite zoo in your area?", "id": "0.7333498226944357", "type": "single", "answers": ["The big one", "The small one", "They're all great"], "question": "What is your favourite zoo in your area?"}
    ]},
    {"id": "3", "title": "Family", "summary": "Family stuff", "questions": [
        {"id": "32", "question": "Have you got any brothers or sisters?", "title": "Have you got any brothers or sisters?", "type": "single", "answers": ["Yes", "No"]},
        {"title": "How many cousines do you have?", "id": "0.09555504354648292", "type": "single", "answers": ["5", "None", "Not sure"], "question": "How many cousines do you have?"}
    ]},
    {"id": "4", "title": "Leasure and entertainment", "summary": "A set of questions about what people do in their spare time", "questions": [
        {"id": "43", "question": "How often do you watch TV?", "title": "How often do you watch TV?", "type": "multiple", "answers": ["Once a week", "Every day", "Dunno"]},
        {"title": "Do you go ofter to the pub with friends?", "id": "0.06497804098762572", "type": "single", "answers": ["Every week", "Quite ofter", "Rarely"], "question": "Do you go ofter to the pub with friends?"}
    ]}
]